Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Artifacts and Memorabilia Collection, 1888-2004 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company. Artifacts and Memorabilia collection 1888-2004 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company.
39 linear feet Extent: 400 Items
Founded in 1864, the J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) is one of the oldest and largest enduring advertising agencies in the United States. Artifacts and Memorabilia span the years 1888 through 2004, and represent a continuation of Record Group 7 of the J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) Archives. It is an artificial collection, the items drawn together from numerous accessions and gathered in one group because of their physical natures and purposes, rather than their Provenance. A significant portion of the objects came from the Epcot Worldwide Manager's Meeting, held in May 1984, at which offices displayed objects they used for New Business promotions, personnel recognitions, and other purposes.
RL.00662
Language: Material in English, Spanish, German
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The J. Walter Thompson Company. Artifacts and Memorabilia Collection were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a transfer in 1989, with additions in subsequent years.
Artifacts and Memorabilia comprise an artificial collection. The items were drawn together from numerous accessions and gathered in one group because of their physical nature rather than their Provenance.
Collection Overview
Artifacts and Memorabilia span the years 1888 through 2004, and represent a continuation of Record Group 7 of the J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) Archives. It is an artificial collection, the items drawn together from numerous accessions and gathered in one group because of their physical natures and purposes, rather than their Provenance. A significant portion of the objects came from the Epcot Worldwide Manager's Meeting, held in May 1984, at which offices displayed objects they used for New Business promotions, personnel recognitions, and other purposes.
Physical storage requirements have necessitated that like items are housed together. Items in the collection have been arranged according to object type. There are 21 object types represented: Awards and Medals; Baseballs; Books; Calendars and Stamps; Christmas Gifts and Ornaments; Coffee Cups and Mugs; Corporate Documents (display items); Desk Objects; Games, Toys, and Equipment; Gifts and Vanity Items; Hats; Invitations and Programs; Logo Stationery Supplies; Plaques; Sculpture and Statues; Sweatshirts and Jackets; Ties and Scarves; Tote Bags; Travel Items; T-Shirts; and Young Tigers Program Memorabilia. In addition, a few items resisted classification, and are grouped as Miscellaneous Items.
Subject Headings
J. Walter Thompson Company; Advertising agencies -- United States -- History; Artifacts; Memorabilia; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
Contents of Collection
- Awards and Medals, 1923-2000 and undated, (14 Boxes)
  - "100 years" medal in lucite block, circa 1964 (Box AM1)
  - Lucite award blocks (Cableshop, Advertising Hall of Fame, Art Director's Club), undated (Box AM1)
  - Medallions for 125th anniversary, circa 1989 (Box AM1)
  - American Association of Advertising Agencies President's Award 1923-1924 (Box AM2)
  - Annual Advertising Award to Stanley Resor, 1948 (Box AM2)
  - Gold Pendants for 125 year JWT celebration, circa 1989 (Box AM2)
  - JWT bronzed medallion celebrating 100 yrs., circa 1964 (Box AM2)
  - JWT bronzed medallion celebrating 100 yrs., circa 1964 (Box AM3)
  - Creative Department Growth Award, 1983 (Box AM4)
  - Engraved metal plate, Copywriter's Hall of Fame to James Webb Young, 1973 (Box AM4)
  - Certificate of merit from 34th annual national competition of outdoor advertising, undated (Box AM5)
  - JWT USA Chairmen's Award, 1983 (Box AM5)
  - Certificates (Box AM6)
    - Advertising Age, 1968-1982 (Box AM6)
    - Advertising Club of New York, Andy Award, 1986 (Box AM6)
    - Advertising Writers' Association of New York, 1966-1967 (Box AM6)
    - American Advertising Federation, Addy Award, 1984 (Box AM6)
    - American Association of Advertising Agencies, membership certificate, undated (Box AM6)
    - American Marketing Association, Effie Award, 1979-1986 and undated (Box AM6)
    - American Television Commercials Festival, 1967, 1985-1986 (Box AM6)
    - Art Direction Magazine, Creativity Award, 1987 (Box AM6)
    - Art Directors' Club of New York, 1966-1983 (Box AM6)
    - Chicago International Film Festival, 1969 and undated (Box AM6)
    - Clio Awards, 1986-1987 (Box AM6)
    - Fortune Charter Advertiser 1930-1965 (Includes a framed JWT house advertisement) (Box AM6)
    - International Film and TV Festival, 1967, 1985 (Box AM6)
    - Kodak Grand Cru, 1990 (Box AM6)
    - London International Advertising Awards (White Castle), 1995 (Box AM6)
    - Miscellaneous award certificates, 1944-1970 (Box AM6)
  - Fortune: Ford Taurus: Best Read Overall Advertising Campaign, undated (Box AM7)
  - Gold wooden box in blue box, TTB awards Malaysia and Thailand, 2000 (Box AM8)
  - Telly Award, 1995 (Box AM9)
  - Sterling silver bowl for Irving Trust, undated (Box AM10)
  - Best of New York: Addy for Reactions, 1991 (Box AM11)
  - Epilepsy Foundation Public Awareness Award, 1999 (Box AM11)
  - Gold Effie: Swinging Bottle, 1994 (Box AM11)
  - Mobius Awards, 1993-1998 (Box AM11)
  - International Automotive Advertising Awards, 1995-1996 (Box AM12)
  - 1st Place Target Award: Ford Explorer Launch, 1995 (Box AM12)
  - 1st Place Target Award: Ford Windstar Launch, 1995 (Box AM12)
  - Gold Effie: For Real, 1994 (Box AM12)
  - Silver Effie: Listerine Antiseptic, 1991 (Box AM12)
  - Gold globe trophy World Highways Expedition/Wallace Elton/JWT Filmways/Ford, 1957 (Box AM13)
  - Medallions for 125th anniversary, circa 1989 (Box AM14)
- Baseballs, undated, (1 Box)
  - JWT stamped signature, undated (Box BB1)
  - JWT with other people's signatures, undated (Box BB1)
  - Rawlings signed by JWT employees, undated (Box BB1)
  - Rawlings with JWT and other signatures, undated (Box BB1)
  - Rawlings with JWT print, undated (Box BB1)
  - Rawlings with plastic wrap and JWT Sticker, undated (Box BB1)
- Books, 1926 and undated, (2 Boxes)
  - Steichen the Photographer by Carl Sandburg, taken from JWT Library, undated (Box BK1)
  - Bound address by President Calvin Coolidge, given before the American Association of Advertising Agencies, 1926 Oct. 27 (Box BK1)
  - Alice in Wonderland books in Spanish, undated (Box BK2)
  - JWT factbook with German or Dutch inside binders, undated (Box BK2)
- Calendars and Stamps, 1914-1993 and undated, (2 Boxes)
  - 18-Month daily activities calender, undated (Box CA1)
  - Agenda, 1993 (Box CA1)
  - Any Year Diary, Tom Sutton International Exchange Program, undated (Box CA1)
  - JWT Italy calender, undated (Box CA1)
  - Album of postage stamps designed by JWT artists, 1967 (Box CA2)
  - JWT daily memorandum, 1914 (Box CA2)
  - JWT London pocket calendar, 1984 (Box CA2)
  - JWT Venezuela calendar, with images of Venezuela, 1983-1984 (Box CA2)
  - Postage stamps, undated (Box CA2)
- Christmas Gifts and Ornaments, 1965-1994 and undated, (4 Boxes)
  - Painted wooden ornaments from JWT Lisbon, undated (Box X1)
  - Bruno Lucchesi terra cotta as Christmas gifts, undated (Box X1)
  - Chicago Office, plastic stocking with knickknacks, undated (Box X1)
  - Detroit Office, Christmas tree ornament, 1988 (Box X1)
  - Detroit Office, ornament celebrating JWT 125th, 1989 (Box X1)
  - Detroit Office fiftieth anniversary ornament, 1994 (Box X1)
  - Thomas Cornell bronze, given as Christmas gift, undated (Box X1)
  - Tiffany's silver owl bookmark, Chicago Christmas, 1982 (Box X1)
  - Swiss Impressions (Christmas gift portfolio commemorating opening of JWT Zurich office), 1965 (Box X2)
  - Various Christmas and New Year's Cards, undated (Box X2)
  - Bottle Christmas JWT Shiraz, 1980 (Box X3)
  - Bottle Christmas JWT White Hermitage wine, 1982 (Box X3)
  - Box JWT Grand Cru Noir red wine, 1981 (Box X3)
  - Can JWT Darjeeling tea, undated (Box X3)
  - Photocopied PR blurb, undated (Box X3)
  - Module/metric sculpture as Christmas gift, 1968 (Box X4)
- Coffee Cups and Mugs, 1975-1993 and undated, (6 Boxes)
  - Black Esso/JWT Worldwide Conference Buzios, Brazil, 1993 March (Box CM1)
  - Black with gold mug, JWT initials, undated (Box CM1)
  - White JWT Scarf mug from Chicago Office, Christmas, 1979 (Box CM1)
  - White, JWT Brentwood, undated (Box CM1)
  - White, JWT Chicago, undated (Box CM1)
  - White, JWT on the Move, 1993 Jan. (Box CM1)
  - White, narrow JWT initials, undated (Box CM1)
  - Blue traveling coffee mug, undated (Box CM2)
  - Silver stein from JWT Detroit for Mike Stocker for 1983-1988, circa 1988 (Box CM2)
  - Pewter stein, undated (Box CM3)
  - Clear 7-Up glass, undated (Box CM4)
  - JWT Brasil demitasse cup and saucer, undated (Box CM4)
  - JWT Chile tankard, undated (Box CM4)
  - JWT coffee cup and saucer, undated (Box CM4)
  - JWT demitasse cup and saucer, undated (Box CM4)
  - JWT Mexico logo, undated (Box CM4)
  - Chicago Office, Christmas, JWT Chicago: Getting Better all the time!, 1975 (Box CM5)
  - J. Walter Reindeer Round-up cowboy boot, undated (Box CM5)
  - JWT USA and Miller, given to employees after winning Miller Account, undated (Box CM5)
  - Renaissance Center, 1983 May (Box CM5)
  - Artistic JWT Picture (Box CM6)
  - Owl logo (Box CM6)
- Corporate Documents, 1893-1994, (6 Boxes)
  - Billing journal, vol. 222, 1923-1937 (Box CD1)
  - Credentials book, circa 1945 (Box CD2)
  - Historic documents (Box CD3)
    - Certification of Board resolution, 1970 (Box CD3)
    - Contract for telephone service, Los Angeles Office, 1938 (Box CD3)
    - Lease on Wrigley Building, Chicago Office, 1924 (Box CD3)
    - Letter from Franklin D. Roosevelt, 1930 (Box CD3)
    - Letter from James Webb Young, regarding 1926 Coolidge speech, 1968 (Box CD3)
    - Letter signed by J. Walter Thompson, 1893 (Box CD3)
    - Letter signed by J. Walter Thompson, 1895 (Box CD3)
    - Letter to Marie Dexter, 1901 (Box CD3)
    - Waiver of Notice of first meeting of Board of Directors, 1907 (Box CD3)
  - Mounted items (Box CD4)
    - Boy Scouts' 75th anniversary, 1985 (Box CD4)
    - Latin America Region's Manager Meeting, Duke University, 1992 (Box CD4)
    - Proclamation from Mayor of New York on JWT 130th anniversary, 1994 (Box CD4)
  - Salary book, New York Office, 1908 (Box CD5)
  - Stock certificates and offers, 1907-1931, 1969 (Box CD6)
- Desk Objects, 1977-2001 and undated, (4 Boxes)
  - Glass paperweight for 75 yrs. Between JWT and Lever Brothers, 1977 (Box D1)
  - JWT ruler Sandton City, undated (Box D1)
  - Waterford crystal baseball paperweight with JWT signature, undated (Box D2)
  - Blue coaster with baseball, JWT LA-San Francisco, 1978 (Box D3)
  - Blue JWT ashtray, undated (Box D3)
  - Business card, JWT Plumbing, undated (Box D3)
  - Business card of Brent Gazzaniga, Creative Group Head of JWT Melbourne, undated (Box D3)
  - Business card of Brent Gazzaniga, International Editor, Austral Publishing Party, Ltd., undated (Box D3)
  - Business card of John E. Peters, senior V.P. of JWT, undated (Box D3)
  - Cardboard coaster from JWT Cares Day holiday party at Heartland Brewery, 1997 (Box D3)
  - Coasters from JWT Greece, Melbourne, undated (Box D3)
  - Crystal Clock: Kraft/JWT Seventy Years and Still Every Second Counts, undated (Box D3)
  - Ford credit mouse pad, undated (Box D3)
  - Heartland Brewery coaster, undated (Box D3)
  - JWT Brentwood coaster, undated (Box D3)
  - JWT wooden stamp, undated (Box D3)
  - Lucite paperweight, JWT grp/merger witth Hill and Knowlton, 1980 (Box D3)
  - Silver business card case from JWT Europe, undated (Box D3)
  - Silver picture frame, Chicago Xmas, undated (Box D3)
  - Wooden letter opener from JWT Brasil, undated (Box D3)
  - Metal pin box, owl logo, original, undated (Box D4)
  - Metal pin box, owl logo, replica made for Senior Partners Council, 1995 (Box D4)
  - Wooden Box with JWT and Owl, circa 2001 (Box D4)
  - Wooden box with owl, JWT Brazil, from Epcot Swap Shop, 1984 (Box D4)
- Games, Toys and Equipment, 1984 and undated, (1 Box)
  - Blue JWT Frisbee, undated (Box G1)
  - Deck of cards with advertisements on the face, undated (Box G1)
  - Frisbee from JWT 1st annual Summer Picnic, undated (Box G1)
  - Golf balls from JWT Atlanta and Manchester offices, undated (Box G1)
  - Incomplete pack of JWT playing cards from Paris office, undated (Box G1)
  - MetLife/Seabury & Smith foam ball, undated (Box G1)
  - Oscar Mayer miniature weiner car, undated (Box G1)
  - Oscar Mayer weiner whistle, undated (Box G1)
  - Pack of JWT playing cards from London office with different advertisements on the faces of the cards, undated (Box G1)
  - Rubik's Cube with JWT logo, JWT Argentina, from Epcot Swap Shop, 1984 (Box G1)
  - Rubik's Cube calendar, JWT Paris, from Epcot Swap Shop, 1984 (Box G1)
  - Top to glue pot, Stick to J. Walter Thompson and Your Business Will Stick to You, undated, undated (Box G1)
- Gift and Vanity Items, 1960-1995 and undated, (2 Boxes)
  - Assorted JWT badges and buttons, undated (Box GV1)
  - Assorted stickers, undated (Box GV1)
  - Belt buckles, undated (Box GV1)
  - Blue canvas set for JWT director's chair, undated (Box GV1)
  - Blue JWT clip, undated (Box GV1)
  - Blue JWT kazoo, undated (Box GV1)
  - Blue JWT vanity plates commemorating 125 years, circa 1989 (Box GV1)
  - Booklet, The Company Store, undated (Box GV1)
  - Brown wooden box lined in velvet containing small bar of Lifebuoy Soap; box inscribed: Lever-JWT 75th Anniv. 1902-1977, includes key, 1977 (Box GV1)
  - Dynamite cracker stick, undated (Box GV1)
  - Gag container of JWT Strength Result pills from JWT Toronto, undated (Box GV1)
  - Gold JWT clip, undated (Box GV1)
  - Green Owl pin, undated (Box GV1)
  - Johnson's Owl soap, undated (Box GV1)
  - JWT 125th Anniversary pins, circa 1989 (Box GV1)
  - JWT belt buckle, undated (Box GV1)
  - JWT Brentwood keychain, undated (Box GV1)
  - JWT Brussels, portable radio player in small Chiclets packaging, 1989 (Box GV1)
  - JWT Cares pin (1994, 1995), 1994-1995 (Box GV1)
  - JWT Chicago Survival Kits, undated (Box GV1)
  - JWT garter, undated (Box GV1)
  - JWT Germany gift guide for 10, 20 and 25 years of service at JWT, undated (Box GV1)
  - JWT keychain, undated (Box GV1)
  - JWT pins, undated (Box GV1)
  - JWT spoon, undated (Box GV1)
  - JWT-TV pocket mirror, undated (Box GV1)
  - Leather wallet, undated (Box GV1)
  - License plates, bumper stickers, pins from Ford Trucks, undated (Box GV1)
  - Manager's Lunacy Kit, undated (Box GV1)
  - Matchbox from JWT London, undated (Box GV1)
  - Matchboxes from JWT Paris (JWT/PPGH), undated (Box GV1)
  - Nametag for Thompson Way Workshop, South Africa (John Furr), 1990 (Box GV1)
  - New penny encased in JWT case, 1991 (Box GV1)
  - Oval Forces of Change sticker, undated (Box GV1)
  - Pin with picture of JWT, undated (Box GV1)
  - Salvation Army tag, undated (Box GV1)
  - Silver bell, undated (Box GV1)
  - Small ceramic dish (Chinese or Japanese), undated (Box GV1)
  - T-Square wall ornament, with T-Square five questions, undated, undated (Box GV1)
  - U.S. Marine Corps key ring, undated (Box GV1)
  - Watch planning cycle from JWT Hong Kong, undated (Box GV1)
  - White pin with Unsung JWT Hero, undated (Box GV1)
  - Wooden eye testing boards from JWT Paris (Chivas Regal), undated (Box GV1)
  - Long-playing record, 15th annual Crystal Ball dinner, 1960 (Box GV2)
  - Long-playing record, 16th annual Crystal Ball dinner, 1961 (Box GV2)
- Hats, 1977-1994 and undated, (1 Box)
  - Ball cap (JWT Young Tigers Hangzhou '94, JWT Melbourne, JWT 130 years, JWT Johannesburg, JWT Detroit Bad boys), undated (Box H1)
  - Bucket hat from NY summer outing, boat trip, 1978 (Box H1)
  - JWT kazoo band cap, undated (Box H1)
  - JWT 130 Years AD Infinitum Hat, 1994 (Box H1)
  - Plastic sun visor (JWT Brasil, NY summer outing Belmont Raceway, and JWT Sao Paulo), 1985 (Box H1)
  - Ski cap, JWT New York, 1977 (Box H1)
  - Straw cowboy hat for Chicago Office Christmas Party Reindeer Roundup, 1984 (Box H1)
  - Woven hat, JWT Young Tigers Thailand, undated (Box H1)
- Invitations and Programs, 1988-1999 and undated, (1 Box)
  - Anniversary Recognition reception, undated (Box IP1)
  - JWT 130 years picnic celebration in NY, 1994 (Box IP1)
  - JWT service anniversary recognition reception, 1999 (Box IP1)
  - N.A.D.A convention in San Francisco, undated (Box IP1)
  - Old Owls Meeting, Duke University, paperwork and handouts, 1995 (Box IP1)
  - Peter's First Christmas, undated (Box IP1)
  - Reception celebrating 50 years with Ford, 1993 (Box IP1)
  - Reception honoring JWT and donation of collection to Duke, in Rare Book Room, 1988 Sept. 26 (Box IP1)
  - Various other, undated (Box IP1)
- Logo Stationery Supplies, 1888-2003 and undated, (5 Boxes)
  - Stationery (1888-1911), including notes written by J. Walter Thompson, 1888-2003 (Box PP1)
  - Announcements, undated (Box PP2)
  - Flyers, programs, etc., undated (Box PP2)
  - JWT blue pen, undated (Box PP2)
  - Menus, etc., undated (Box PP2)
  - Trade cards, undated (Box PP2)
  - JWT Haricot pen, undated (Box PP3)
  - JWT Chile paper pad, undated (Box PP3)
  - JWT Detroit heart-shaped pad and pencil, undated (Box PP3)
  - JWT Melbourne paper pad, undated (Box PP3)
  - JWT Parker pen from EPCOT's manager meeting, circa 1984 (Box PP3)
  - JWT pens and pencils (from Mexico,Chicago and NY), undated (Box PP3)
  - JWT San Francisco office memo carrier, undated (Box PP3)
  - JWT TV pad and pen, undated (Box PP3)
  - JWT script roll holder, undated (Box PP3)
  - Pack of JWT copywriters pencils (length of line drawn), undated (Box PP3)
  - Archives Weekend folder (Honourably Retired Directors) Duke University, 1990 May 25-27 (Box PP4)
  - Archives Weekend folders (Second Retired Directors) Duke University, 1990 May 31-June 2 (Box PP4)
  - The Year of the Tiger pamphlet, undated (Box PP4)
  - Clear plastic JWT Europe paper holder, undated (Box PP4)
  - Color card in Portuguese from JWT Brasil, 1993 (Box PP4)
  - Colored pencil set, undated (Box PP4)
  - Envelope celebrating 50 yrs, the Phillipines and a JWT url, undated (Box PP4)
  - Gray folder, undated (Box PP4)
  - JWT Detroit foil bag, undated (Box PP4)
  - JWT Detroit type paper, undated (Box PP4)
  - JWT envelope, undated (Box PP4)
  - JWT Europe agenda, undated (Box PP4)
  - JWT Inter-Department Mail envelope, undated (Box PP4)
  - JWT navy blue folder, undated (Box PP4)
  - JWT notepad, undated (Box PP4)
  - JWT notepad, Amsterdam, undated (Box PP4)
  - JWT NY card envelope, undated (Box PP4)
  - JWT Sao Paulo evelope, undated (Box PP4)
  - JWT Sydney briefcase folder, undated (Box PP4)
  - JWT Toronto/Budget all-star brochure, undated (Box PP4)
  - Large JWT NY mail envelopes, undated (Box PP4)
  - News release JWT letterhead, undated (Box PP4)
  - Newspaper and JWT Venezuela paraphernalia, undated (Box PP4)
  - Note containing letter and picture from Commodore's Cup folder from JWT Chicago, 1993 (Box PP4)
  - Pieces of JWT typing paper of Nancy S. Fitzpatrick, undated (Box PP4)
  - Purchase order forms from JWT New York, undated (Box PP4)
  - Purple cotton embroidered oriental folder, filled with material from Asia-Pacific Media Conference, undated (Box PP4)
  - Travel authorization sheet, revised, 1990 (Box PP4)
  - Blue JWT Box containing various materials, undated (Box PP5)
- Plaques, 1978-2004 and undated, (9 Boxes)
  - JWT and Ford Dealers 50 Year Partners, circa 1993 (Box P1)
  - JWT Archives sign, undated (Box P1)
  - Lucite plaques featuring David Starr Jordan quote, undated (Box P1)
  - Plain tableweights (Ford, Sam Meek), undated (Box P1)
  - Best Read Advertising in Fortune, Eastman Kodak Company, 1984 (Box P2)
  - Black JWT company American Red Cross Campaign 1958-1978, circa 1978 (Box P2)
  - Black JWT company American Red Cross Campaign 35 years, undated (Box P2)
  - North America Innovation Workshop, Duke University, 1992 (Box P2)
  - Wood and silver JWT and Quaker Oats Silver Anniversary, 1978 (Box P3)
  - 1996 International Print Advertising: Blends/Reduces/Sticks, 1996 (Box P4)
  - Girl Scouts: Tomorrow's Power Take Control of Life, undated (Box P4)
  - Henry Ford II Memorial Golf Classic, undated (Box P4)
  - International Television Advertising, Mel/Erin/Clarisse, undated (Box P4)
  - Montreux Detroit Jazz Festival 1996, 1996-1999 (Box P4)
  - Silver Effie, Making the Road a Safer Place, 1998 (Box P4)
  - Silver Effie, The only way to get there, 1998 (Box P4)
  - Bronze celebrating various volunteer efforts, undated (Box P5, P6)
  - Wooden plaque of certificates of 100 shares of JWT common stock, undated (Box P7)
  - Mustang Museum, Proclamation of Appreciation, undated (Box P8)
  - JWT/Mazda Global Business Partnership, Lisbon, 2004 (Box P9)
- Sculptures and Statues, 1968-2001 and undated, (5 Boxes)
  - Bronze relief portrait of Stanley Resor, 1969 (Box SS1)
  - Owl sculptures (JWT Paris, Peru, Germany), different media, undated (Box SS1)
  - Brick sculpture, similar to JWT Christmas gifts, undated (Box SS2)
  - Carved wooden box, painted from JWT South America, undated (Box SS2)
  - Module/metric sculpture as Christmas gift, 1968 (Box SS2)
  - Untitled sculptures for New York, Christmas, 1968 (Box SS2)
  - Executive Group Meeting Box, 2001 (Box SS3)
  - JWT outline door statue, undated (Box SS3)
  - JWT shark and wood sculpture, undated (Box SS3)
  - Marble slab for JWT Board of Directors Meeting, Detroit, 1993 (Box SS3)
  - Pyramid Good Fortune candle for JWT 130th anniversary, 1994 (Box SS3)
  - JWT Malaysia puppet display, undated (Box SS4)
  - Travelling archive module and poster of replicas of JWT NY gates, undated (Box SS5)
- Sweatshirts and Jackets, 1990s and undated, (2 Boxes)
  - JWT Detroit, undated (Box SJ1)
  - JWT Europe, undated (Box SJ1)
  - JWT event at Duke University, 1990s (Box SJ1)
  - JWT Sydney Hunt-a-valet, undated (Box SJ1)
  - Simple JWT embroidery, undated (Box SJ1)
  - Japanese Pajamas from JWT Tokyo, undated (Box SJ2)
  - JWT Brasil white and blue starter jacket, undated (Box SJ2)
  - JWT Chicago green starter jacket, undated (Box SJ2)
- Ties and Scarves, 1970s-1990 and undated, (2 Boxes)
  - Blue tie, Archives Weekend, Duke University, 1990 May 25-27 (Box T1)
  - Blue with gold owls tie, JWT Peru, undated (Box T1)
  - Blue with orange owls tie and bowtie, JWT Amsterdam, undated (Box T1)
  - Blue with orange stripes tie, Given to officers and Directors, undated (Box T1)
  - Blue with white owls tie, JWT Mexico, undated (Box T1)
  - Blue with white owls tie, JWT Venezuela 20th Anniversary, undated (Box T1)
  - JWT blue scarf, Chicago Office, undated (Box T1)
  - JWT blue, orange, and tan Scarf, 1970s (Box T1)
  - JWT light and dark blue scarf, undated (Box T1)
  - JWT Reindeer Roundup blue scarf, undated (Box T1)
  - Blue with orange owls tie (20, 25, 30, 35, 40 Years), undated (Box T2)
  - JWT picture tie, undated (Box T2)
- Tote Bags, 1976-1984 and undated, (1 Box)
  - Blue, leather trim JWT Brasil, undated (Box TB1)
  - JWT USA with ratings chart for 1981-1983, circa 1984 (Box TB1)
  - Small blue JWT Chicago, Christmas gift, 1976 (Box TB1)
- Travel Items, undated, (1 Box)